const javascript = [
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is es8 0',
    answer: 'the future',
    reference: 'mdn: es8',
    id: 0,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is this 1',
    answer: 'no idea',
    reference: 'every programmer',
    id: 1,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is destructuring 2',
    answer: 'deleting life',
    reference: 'good vibes',
    id: 2,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is redux 3',
    answer: 'life',
    reference: 'good vibes',
    id: 3,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is es8 4',
    answer: 'the future',
    reference: 'mdn: es8',
    id: 4,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is this 5',
    answer: 'no idea',
    reference: 'every programmer',
    id: 5,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is destructuring 6',
    answer: 'deleting life',
    reference: 'good vibes',
    id: 6,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is redux 7',
    answer: 'life',
    reference: 'good vibes',
    id: 7,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is es8 8',
    answer: 'the future',
    reference: 'mdn: es8',
    id: 8,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is this 9',
    answer: 'no idea',
    reference: 'every programmer',
    id: 9,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is destructuring 10',
    answer: 'deleting life',
    reference: 'good vibes',
    id: 10,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is redux 11',
    answer: 'life',
    reference: 'good vibes',
    id: 11,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is es8 12',
    answer: 'the future',
    reference: 'mdn: es8',
    id: 12,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is this 13',
    answer: 'no idea',
    reference: 'every programmer',
    id: 13,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is destructuring 14',
    answer: 'deleting life',
    reference: 'good vibes',
    id: 14,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is redux 15',
    answer: 'life',
    reference: 'good vibes',
    id: 15,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is es8 16',
    answer: 'the future',
    reference: 'mdn: es8',
    id: 16,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is this 17',
    answer: 'no idea',
    reference: 'every programmer',
    id: 17,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is destructuring 18',
    answer: 'deleting life',
    reference: 'good vibes',
    id: 18,
  },
  { 
    logo: 'js',
    question: 'what is redux 19',
    answer: 'life',
    reference: 'good vibes',
    id: 19,
  },
]

module.exports.javascript = javascript